<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mendo</title>
    <description>Hi</description>
    <link>http://salmendo.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://salmendo.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 21:23:24 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 21:23:24 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cúrsame</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cúrsame is an up and coming educational platform for schools. I worked with the team for about one year and was in charge of completely rethinking the whole platform´s user experience and design, as well as executing a huge Ruby on Rails integration replacing the old design.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/26/cursame.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/26/cursame.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SomosFut</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;SomosFut is a soccer platform the enables field administrators and amateur soccer players to interact based on games, teams, and scores. I started from scratch designing all aspects of aesthetics and user experience, later chopping it into html and css.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/25/somosfut.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/25/somosfut.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Intrinno</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Joining the team at Intrinno, an open innovation platform for companies, I was tasked with improving the overall design and user experience of their current platform; after that I took care of the code and pushed it into their Angular.js based app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/24/intrinno.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/24/intrinno.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kueski</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Before becoming México´s leading online lender, I was there helping Kueski´s two cofounders to design the inital beta pages and arrive at the first platform, later taking it into a second interation loop improving the design and user experience, all while coding it into their Sinatra app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/23/kueski.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/23/kueski.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prestadero</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When Prestadero, a peer-to-peer lending site, was looking for someone to retouch their platform, the founder contacted me and I continued on to completly rethink the overall user experience and design, following up with html and css implementation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/22/prestadero.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/22/prestadero.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reviews.co.uk</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Reviews.co.uk is an online reviews site, now boasting thousands of them; back in the day, I helped them with the execution of a completely new user experience and design platform.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/21/reviews-co-uk.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/21/reviews-co-uk.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boxtuffs</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This little box was a personal project that I started in my free time about designing little ui elements, then coding and uploading them for people to see/download, back when html5 and css3 was starting to hit the web.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/20/boxtuffs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/20/boxtuffs.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SendRead</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;SendRead was a side project I was doing with a few of my friends that let you save links to your account so they could be read later; I was in charge of the user experience and design aspect of the app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://salmendo.com/2015/04/19/send-read.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://salmendo.com/2015/04/19/send-read.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
